The rules keep changing.
I've been rehearsing every possible outcome.
Once this thought arises, there is no more room for right or wrong.
I am resolved to sever this flood
so that my soul can break free from mediocrity,
from loneliness and distinction.
One more step and you'll fall into madness.
Don't fall down.
I look towards the top.
Chase !
Refined to perfection.
Never retreat, no matter the danger.
I dare to defy the heavens !
Always overcome the obstacles,
ignite the seas with blood,
bloom through trials and tribulations.
Even the sharpest thorns
will be reduced into ashes.
What is there to fear ?
Renegade Immortal\NSubtitles by Bonobosubs\Nhttps://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
The celestial spiritual energy fluctuations are intense...
There must be a celestial artifact inside !
Indeed !
When I came here earlier,
I didn't see any formations.
In just a few months,
how could such a massive formation appear here ?
Brother Shengong arrived early !
You're the one who's late.
On my way here,
I had the honor of meeting Senior.
You met my Master ?
Senior also gave some instructions.
We must be careful on this trip.
This formation is indeed somewhat strange.
The formation broke too quickly...
It broke !
Quick !
The formation is open !
Something's wrong !
This is bad !
What in the world is this thing !?
I am...
finally...
back !
Run !
Today
is the day of my rebirth !
Main fragment\NThunder Celestial Realm
We will reach the Celestial Realm Gate in half a day,
but we still haven't encountered a single person.
Brother Xu,
what's wrong ?
What is this thing ?
The power of this arm
is close to Nirvana Scryer !
It...
can devour thunder !
This is bad !
I won't survive if it hits me.
I need to use my Third-Eye spell.
Stop !
This battle
was the most perilous one I have had
since I reached Corporeal Yang.
This severed arm is too weird.
No wonder the road was deserted...
This thing most likely killed everyone.
There's more than one severed limb.
It gathers blood energy through slaughter.
It's probably using this energy to reassemble its body.
If that's the case,
its true cultivation...
...is definitely beyond what we can deal with.
Let's go,
we must quickly leave the Celestial Realm.
White-haired old man
Qing Shui, oh Qing Shui...
You really dismembered me alive back then
and sealed me here...
Who would have thought that after tens of thousands of years,
I...
would still be here !
You didn't expect this, did you ?
It was your seal
that shielded me
from the collapse of the Celestial Realm back then !
How many years has it been ?
I finally...
can smell some living people once again !
So many Qi Refiners have come
to the Thunder Celestial Realm.
Very good.
They should allow me to recover my cultivation a little bit.
We're almost there.
Move !
Let me through !
Wait !
The gate is open !
Quick !
This way !
Why do Qi Refiners nowadays
have so little origin energy ?
No one
is allowed to leave the Thunder Celestial Realm today !
He's closing the Celestial Realm Gate !
It's over...
We can't get out !
Fellow cultivators,
if the gate closes,
we'll all be trapped here !
Follow me to kill him !
A monster...
Run !
Trying to flee now ?
Brother Xu,
I'm afraid we won't be able to leave this place.
Bland...
so bland...
It's hopeless,
we're all going to die !
Members of the Zhan Family,
join my formation !
Tang Family,
face the enemy !
We cultivators
would rather die fighting than live in submission !
The Sun Family
will not retreat !
The Lu Family will not retreat !
The Zheng Family will not retreat !
We'll die either way,
so let's fight at full strength !
That's right,
fight him !
Charge !
Kill him !
How interesting...
It's pretty impressive.
Explode !
Thunderbolt...
Slash !
This sword strike
isn't too bad.
Lock the Origin,
Trap the Soul !
Kunji Cauldron,
suppress !
What a pity...
Compared to the strength of the Celestial Realm back then,
you are
laughably weak !
Today,
all living beings in this realm
shall become sacrifices.
Avatars\NCelestial Spell
This man's cultivation is sky high
and he acts with ruthless cruelty.
Brother Xu,
perhaps we should retreat deeper into the Celestial Realm.
I'll use all my knowledge to set up defensive restrictions.
Maybe we can hold out until he leaves.
It's useless.
He is most likely an Ancient Celestial.
Hiding from him in the Celestial Realm
is the same as waiting for death.
Time to clear the area.
Brother Li,
do you trust me ?
Of course I do !
Brother Xu,
why are you asking ?
I have a spell that allows me
to merge with the world
and vanish without a trace.
If you trust me,
I'll give it my all.
Brother Xu,
please go ahead and use your spell.
I, Li Yuan,
am willing to take this gamble !
Okay.
Ordinary Spatial Bending won't be enough
to deceive this person.
I must completely merge my body
with the world.
The Dao has no form,
clear the mind and the soul,
return to the origin.
The Dao of merging with the world ?
Even back in the days,
only a handful of people
could master such a spell.
Interesting !
Show yourself
before me !
Master ?
It's Master !
Explode !
I remember now.
You are the Qi Refiner
who escaped from my Ji Realm.
“Celestial Lord Qing Shui, no matter how strong your seal was, it couldn’t beat the passage of time. You wouldn’t dare to kill me.\NIf you wanted to kill me, why did you place a healing formation outside the sealing formation!? However, I have to thank you, because if you had not sealed me, I fear I wouldn’t have survived the collapse of the Celestial Realm!\N“Qing Shui, since I didn’t die, you naturally aren’t dead either. Unless you can find another sealing vortex left behind by the Ancient Celestial Realm, you will not seal me again!” The white-haired man had a ferocious expression as he laughed wildly and charged into the void.\N\NAs the fragment collapsed, a monstrous flame shot out from within. There was a flash of red light and then an eye flew out. The person grabbed the eye and placed it inside his right eye socket.\N\N“The Ji Realm was sealed into the right eye, but too much of it was consumed back in the Celestial Realm War. It will be very difficult to replenish it, but it is not impossible! However, I have just escaped, so my cultivation is only at 10%. I must restore my celestial origin energy as soon as possible.”\N-----\NThe reason Wang Lin asks Li Yuan if he trusts him is because he isn't sure if he can use Spatial Bending to transport someone else safely.\N\NLi Yuan was startled and nodded. “Does Brother Xu have a method of leaving? I naturally believe in Brother Xu!”\N\NWang Lin hesitated before slowly saying, “I indeed have a spell, but I have not fully mastered it yet. If I take a person with me, while it won't harm me, the person I bring will likely suffer. If you agree, I can try it.”
Ask
Qi Condensation
the perilous path filled with countless blades.
Foundation Establishment
Can the mundane world be shattered
Core Formation
Nascent Soul
by a child's steadfast heart ?
If the laws of this world
Soul Formation
Soul Transformation
stand in the way,
I'll defy the universe to tread the heavens
Ascendant
and ask this question to the sky.
My heart's deepest wish
is to not kneel before these mountains and rivers.
Don't accept your doomed fate,
karma can be changed.
Unwilling to let go,
my obsessions propel me forward.
Don't be afraid.
Thunder rumbles as I dare to tread through the reincarnation cycle.
Accept your fate and stay mortal or defy it to become immortal.
Hold fast to this resolve and break through the obstacles.
I'll fight all those who dare to stand in my way.
Let the winds of war heed my command.
I sign this question with my heart.
What is the Dao ?
Defying the flow of heaven and earth,
the heart I cultivate stays true.
I contemplate the wisdom of heaven and earth.
I shall choose my path between karma and fate.
My unshakable Dao Heart
aspires to ascend.
Defying,
this is what my journey to treading the heavens relies on.
Accept your fate and stay mortal or defy it to become immortal.
Hold fast to this resolve and break through the obstacles.
I'll fight all those who dare to stand in my way.
Let the winds of war heed my command.
I sign this question with my heart.
What is the Dao ?
Defying the flow of heaven and earth,
the heart I cultivate stays true.
I contemplate the wisdom of heaven and earth.
I shall choose my path between karma and fate.
My unshakable Dao Heart
aspires to ascend.
Defying,
this is what my journey to treading the heavens relies on.